import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const benWQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 152,
    question: "Who completed the Twelve Labors?",
    options: ["Heracles", "Caecillius", "Coeus"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 153,
    question: "Who turned into a spider after challenging Athena?",
    options: ["Selene", "Arachne", "Theia"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 154,
    question: "Who was the Titan who held up the sky?",
    options: ["Themis", "Atlas", "Galatea"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 155,
    question: "Who stole fire from the gods for humans?",
    options: ["Prometheus", "Ullyses", "Hercules"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 156,
    question: "What river did souls cross to reach the underworld?",
    options: ["The River Styx", "The river Parthenon", "The river Lethe"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 157,
    question: "What is Tartarus?",
    options: ["The deepest part of the underworld", "The Utopia beyond the underworld", "The place between the mortals and the gods"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 158,
    question: "Who guarded the gates of the underworld?",
    options: ["Cerberus", "Charon", "Hades"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 159,
    question: "Who was the god of dreams?",
    options: ["Tethys", "Hyperion", "Morpheus"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 160,
    question: "Who crafted the labyrinth?",
    options: ["Cronus", "Daedalus", "Scylla"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 161,
    question: "What fruit seeds did Persephone eat?",
    options: ["Pomegranate", "Starfruit", "Peaches"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 162,
    question: "Who wounded Aphrodite during the Trojan War?",
    options: ["Priapus", "Diomedes", "Menelaus"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 163,
    question: "Which mortal was turned into a laurel tree?",
    options: ["Helen", "Rhea", "Daphne"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 164,
    question: "Who was the personification of the sun before Apollo?",
    options: ["Helios", "Tyche", "Hecuba"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 165,
    question: "What was the punishment of Tantalus?",
    options: ["Eternal pain", "Eternal exhaustion", "Eternal thirst and hunger"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 151,
    question: "Who was the giant with a single eye that was blinded by Odysseus?",
    options: ["Polyphemus", "Agammemnon", "Typhon"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }
];